Guide to the Don Patinkin Papers, 1870-1995
Don Patinkin papers 1870-1995
- Miscellaneous Series, ca. 1930-1990and undated (Bulk 1950-1980)
  - Other Writings and Speeches Subseries
    - Revisions of Books: MIP, KMT, Chicago Essay, Anticipations of General Theory
    - Articles, 1972-1977, (3 folders)
    - Articles, 1946-1958, (3 folders)
    - Articles, 1958-1972, (3 folders)
    - Hebrew Materials
    - Oil Policy, Articles and Writings
    - Hebrew Papers
    - Kuznets Article and Speech by Levhari and Sheshinski
    - Articles/Printed Material
    - Articles (M-Z)
    - Articles
    - The History of the US Income and Product Accounts: Development of an Analytical Tool, 1971
    - Revisions of Books: MIP, KMT, Chicago Essays, Anticipations (Box 78)
    - Abstracts, Memorial Lectures, Book Reviews, Miscellaneous
    - Patinkin Articles, 1946-1957, (2 folders)
    - Patinkin Articles, 1958-1967, (2 folders)
    - Patinkin Articles, 1968-1971, (2 folders)
    - Articles Alphabetized by Author's Last Name, A-C, (3 folders)
    - Articles Alphabetized by Author's Last Name, D-M, (9 folders) (Box 79)
    - Historian of Thought: American Economist (Box 80)
    - Patinkin Articles, 1975-1983, (2 folders)
    - Patinkin Articles, 1984-1989, (2 folders)
    - Patinkin Articles,1990, (2 folders)
    - Articles Alphabetized by Author's Last Name, N-Z, (11 folders)
    - Keynes and his Interpreters
  - Other Materials Subseries
    - Invoices,1962 (Box 80)
    - House Packing Receipts
    - Bibliography and Computer Print-out
    - Photographs of Patinkin, (4 items)